FAUSTO ARIEL LORENZO





IT customer service specialist with knowledge and hands-on experience in all aspects of web development and system administration. Enthusiastic team player and willing to go above and beyond to make sure the work is done efficiently.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- Excellent programming and design skills
- Strong system administration knowledge
- Proficient in Python, C#, PHP, SQL, JavaScript, React, Vue, VB.NET, HTML, CSS, AJAX, XML, C, Java
- Strong collaborative and problem-solving skills
- ASP.NET MVC and WebForms, Django, Flask, PHP/MySQL
- Bash, PowerShell

EXPERIENCE

KP & Sons Automotive - Customer Support

NOVEMBER 2019 - MARCH 2020

- Activate and manage the infrastructure of the devices in the office, including networking, computer maintenance
- Manage and assist in website creation (SVG, Wordpress)
- Assist in company advertising and graphic design (SVG)

Keypoint Intelligence - Software Engineer

JANUARY 2018 - NOVEMBER 2018

- Built back-end database SQL Server functions and procedures for the company website, bliQ (SQL, SQL Server)
- Assist in the overall change of the back-end intranet applications (ASP.NET WebForms, C#, VB.NET)
- Drastically improve runtime and execution of procedures and functions (SQL Server, T-SQL)

SAI Global - Software Engineer

MAY 2017 - OCTOBER 2017

- Built and deployed a large amount of web courses (HTML5, JavaScript, XML)
- Repaired and made recommendations on courses built either by me or other employees (HTML5, JavaScript, XML)

Information Systems, Southern Adventist University - Web Developer

MAY 2016 - JANUARY 2017

- Recreated the back-end functionality for the university account login site still used today (ASP.NET MVC, C#,, HTML5,CSS, JavaScript, jQuery)
- Design front-end view of main site search for students that is still used today (ASP.NET MVC, C#, Bootstrap, HTML5,CSS, JavaScript, jQuery)
- Assist in project planning and fix current projects (ASP.NET MVC, C#, Angular, HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery)

School of Education & Psychology, Southern Adventist University - Computer Lab Manager

SEPTEMBER 2015 - AUGUST 2016

- Assessed customer needs and made recommendations
- Implemented agreed upon solutions and employee rotation schedule
- Changed the look and content of the department site (HTML, CSS)

🚅 IRON

Online Campus, Southern Adventist University - Web Programming Specialist

MAY 2015 - JANUARY 2016

- Created back-end functionality for the university web tools online directory still used today (PHP/MySQL, C#, .NET)
- Made recommendations on web software for online classes that are still used today (PHP/MySQL)

EDUCATION

Southern Adventist University, Collegedale, TN - B.S. Computer Systems Administration

JULY 2011 - DECEMBER 2016

• Coursework in networking, programming, software development, computer architectures, databases, serveradministration, and virtualization